{
    "quizData": [
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "",
            "answer": "",
            "b": "",
            "c": "",
            "d": "",
            "question": ""
        },
        {
            "a": "Sayantan",
            "answer": "c",
            "b": "Bose",
            "c": "Sayantan Bose",
            "d": "Bose Sayantan",
            "question": "What is your name?"
        },
        {
            "a": "a",
            "answer": "d",
            "b": "b",
            "c": "c",
            "d": "d",
            "question": "My name is?"
        },
        {
            "a": "b",
            "answer": "e",
            "b": "c",
            "c": "d",
            "d": "e",
            "question": "a"
        },
        {
            "a": "Sayantan",
            "answer": "c",
            "b": "Bose",
            "c": "Sayantan Bose",
            "d": "Bose Sayantan",
            "question": "What is your name?"
        },
        {
            "a": "b",
            "answer": "d",
            "b": "c",
            "c": "d",
            "d": "e",
            "question": "a"
        },
        {
            "a": "c",
            "answer": "c",
            "b": "d",
            "c": "e",
            "d": "f",
            "question": "b"
        },
        {
            "a": "a",
            "answer": "e",
            "b": "b",
            "c": "c",
            "d": "d",
            "question": "What is your name?"
        },
        {
            "a": "b",
            "answer": "b",
            "b": "c",
            "c": "d",
            "d": "e",
            "question": "a"
        },
        {
            "a": "b",
            "answer": "c",
            "b": "c",
            "c": "d",
            "d": "e",
            "question": "a"
        },
        {
            "a": "2",
            "answer": "1",
            "b": "3",
            "c": "4",
            "d": "5",
            "question": "1"
        },
        {
            "a": "Sayantan",
            "answer": "c",
            "b": "Bose",
            "c": "Sayantan Bose",
            "d": "Bose Sayantan",
            "question": "What is your name?"
        },
        {
            "a": "a",
            "answer": "d",
            "b": "b",
            "c": "c",
            "d": "d",
            "question": "What is your name?"
        },
        {
            "a": "d",
            "answer": "h",
            "b": "e",
            "c": "f",
            "d": "h",
            "question": "What is your name?"
        },
        {
            "a": "b",
            "answer": "e",
            "b": "c",
            "c": "d",
            "d": "e",
            "question": "a"
        }
    ]
}